<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="tap_to_call">Tap the top to call %1s or bottom to cancel.</string>
    <string name="app_name">Talking Caller</string>

	<string name="settings">设置</string>
	<string name="instructions">指示</string>
	
    <string name="welcome_note">2 您打開  Talking Caller. For instruction press the menu button</string>
    <string name="welcome_note_with_instruction">You opened Talking Caller. Instruction, 
    	Slide from top or bottom to scroll over the list, tap the screen once to hear the name of the contact,
    	tap the same location on the screen to call, click the menu button for speed settings</string>
    <string name="sequence_length_pref">Initial Sequence Length</string>
     
	<string name="speed_settings">Click the bottom left screen to edit the speed settings or bottom right for other instructions</string>
	
	<string name="saved_preferences">Saved your preferences. Back to your contact List</string>
	<string name="cancel_preferences">Canceled your preferences. Back to your contact List</string>
	<string name="call_start">Start calling %1s</string>
	<string name="call_cancel">Call canceled. Back to your contact List</string>
	
	<string name="testing_phrase">您打開 I am testing the speed of my voice</string>
	<string name="testing_speed_up_phrase">Speed Up. I am testing the speed of my voice</string>
	<string name="testing_speed_down_phrase">Speed Down. I am testing the speed of my voice</string>
    <string name="slowest_testing_phrase">This is the slowest i can go</string>
    <string name="fastest_testing_phrase">This is the fastest i can go</string>
    <string name="instructions_speech">Instruction.\nSlide from top or bottom to scroll over the list.\nTap 
    	the screen once to hear the name of the contact.\nTap the same location on the screen to call. \nTap 
    	the bottom of the screen to go back to your contact list</string>
    <string name="back_to_your_contact_list">Back to your contact List</string>
    
 	<string name="open_preferences">Preferences. Are you visually impaired? Tap the top if yes and i would provide a
 		special preferences screen for you.
 	</string>
	<string name="speed_setting_special">Speed Settings. Click the top to speed up the voice, middle to make it slower,
		 bottom left to save and bottom right to cancel</string>   
 </resources>
